A man who lives in a room which has nothing,
where everything is anomalous...
Vincent Law.
What was he thinking while in here?
What was it he so wanted
that he was prepared to die for it?
And this is all I find.
Re-l Mayer!
He's only an immigrant...
Who were you anyway?
Guess this means I can't find anything when Iggy's not around.
The projected escape route
of infected autoreivs?
How is this possible?
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
meditation    sing the future, future of hades
Who is it?
This way.
Nothing there
was a city, church, or a river,
not color, light, or shadow.
Re-l Mayer...
In the end, she is unfit.
What...?
Who...?
Yes, that's it.
Yes, you're a clever one, Pino.
Pino...
It's hot here.
Dorothy, please turn on the AC-
You are...
the infected autoreiv!
For a time,
not moving in the slightest,
I felt the indescribably immense tide,
the serenity of the vast sky,
and the melancholy of the hour
spread pleasantly through every fiber of my being.
That... was a waking dream.
This isn't what it seems!
In the end, once an immigrant, always an immigrant.
...by yourself.
God, it was a terrible dream.
The Security Bureau mistook me for your killer, Dorothy.
What a ridiculous nightmare.
Don't you agree, Dorothy?
As if I'd-
Don't suck up to an Entourage.
Dorothy's gone.
You cannot become a model citizen.
I do not know
what happened within my psyche,
nor am I able to express what did happen.
I...
As a model citizen...
I've been trying very hard
to become a model citizen.
I...
You are a criminal,
Vincent Law.
No!
That is reality.
Help me!
That moment, when you felt something go to sleep within you
and something awakened,
was a moment that defied description.
In that world born of him,
everyone could become anything they wanted to be.
Those are Joe Bousquet's words.
Who?
Joe Bousquet.
Joe...
You are Vincent Law, correct?
Where am I...?
There's nothing to worry about.
Your body overcame the virus.
Though, that was really due to my treatment.
Eighty percent of the people who come here
are infected and last barely a week.
Infected...
Indeed.
You've been sleeping for ten days.
You're fine now.
Ten...
I heard many things during that time...
from Pino.
Ah, there you are, Pino.
Vincent is awake.
Vince!
Good morning!
I'm glad,
Vince.
Pi... no.
The autoreivs' escape route...
No wonder the Security Bureau guys can't find it.
Um...
Joe-san.
Joe?
Joe...
Joe!
Ah, please excuse me.
No, I am Hoody.
Joe is a poet from Carcassonne.
Why are you...
so nice to someone like me?
You'll get into trouble too...
We were also once protected
with warmth, tolerance, and security
in that place.
The city must still be as beautiful as it has always been, no?
That city...
Everything's a big fat lie!
Lies are truth until you know them to be lies.
It may be the right thing to do to discern truth from lies,
but that does not mean it will bring happiness.
Are lies happiness?
That's right.
You're a clever child, Pino.
Let me take a good look at you.
Wonderful.
So, autoreivs are becoming more and more like us after all.
Are these types common over there now?
"Over there"?
What are you talking about?
About Romdeau.
"Romdeau..."
It makes me nostalgic.
Wait a minute.
This isn't the immigrant sector?!
Why am I still alive?
Why are you asking the obvious?
You escaped out of the dome with her, didn't you?
"Out of the dome"?
Yes, yes!
I know!
The dome is 1246.65 units away from here.
And the distance from the ground to
the plugvent Vince jumped down from
is approximately 517 units.
I took a good look and asked around,
so I know a whole lot!
Aren't I wonderful?
Right, Vince?
Vince...
Outside...
of Romdeau...
Vince!
You seem kind of down.
Maybe it's due to an injury from the last treatment.
Or maybe it's because you got fired by the Representative.
They even took Iggy away.
That's cruel of them.
No.
It's not because of that.
Then what happened?
Please tell me.
No.
I can't.
Oh.
You're worried about Bruce and Gatalie.
They're fine.
I've made a few modifications, actually.
Nothing will get passed on to anyone.
Grandfather wouldn't permit something like that-
It's our secret.
Even before being your primary care physician,
I am your friend.
You'll trust me,
right,
Re-l?
You won't tell anyone?
Of course not.
I found it...
PROXY's corpse.
Not even the Security Bureau knows yet.
That's the monster that Raul is looking for
while keeping it a secret from even the Intelligence Bureau.
I need a favor.
Please analyze it and tell me what you find.
Grandfather also kept it a secret.
I want to find out what it is for
myself with my own two eyes and feet.
Knowing may not necessarily make you happy-
I don't care.
Please,
Daedalus.
Fine.
I'll do as you say.
Will you tell me where it is?
Without a doubt,
I fell from there.
Chased by a monster,
framed for a crime, and treated as a rebel...
A monster, you say?
So you saw it?
"It..."
You know of it?
It...
They...
are demons born from the enraged land.
Note: In Hindu and Buddhist mythology, Amrita is the drink of the gods, which           grants them immortality. The word itself literally means "without death".
The supposedly immortal amrita cells...
actually died?
What do you think?
Er, well...
I'll have to take it back to the lab and
run tests before I can make any guesses.
You knew.
You would be better off forgetting
everything you've seen here.
This is PROXY, isn't it?
And...
There is another monster
that killed this one.
It should be alive somewhere.
You-
Re-l.
You know, don't you, Daedalus?
I'm sorry.
Of course you can't talk about it.
No, I-
It's all right, Daedalus.
I guess I got you into trouble.
I just want you to let me handle the rest.
So, please promise me.
You never found anything here.
Nope.
You could even say that I've never been here before.
That's good.
Well, I'll leave the rest to you.
Please prepare a dossier when the results come out.
I'll come ask you about them next time.
Where are you going?
I told you, didn't I?
I want to investigate on my own.
There is an escape route over here
that only infected autoreivs know about.
I am going beyond that route.
Re-l...
I hear you're an immigrant.
I guess Romdeau didn't suit you.
I know how you feel.
You're welcome here, then.
Stay as long as you want.
There is freedom here.
We left the dome and won true freedom.
What's that?
At the dome, they toss what they don't need anymore.
But most of it is still useful.
I found this too!
People here have left Romdeau for various reasons
or have been exiled from the city.
As a result, there are many who are hostile towards Romdeau,
although there are some who wish to go back.
But,
it's said that you can never go back.
Who said that?
A lady I met over that way.
Quinn?
That bitch.
Come to think of it, the old man was saying
that this one was a top-of-the-line luxury item.
I bet high-class citizens were using her.
Then maybe they'll come for this "lost-and-found", eh Miss?
Vince!
I'm just kidding.
Who'd go back to a place like that, anyhow?
Right?
True enough.
True enough!
What am I going to do now?
So you're the one with Pino-chan?
I'm Quinn.
As you can see, I pick up stuff that's been tossed into the ocean.
It's a pretty good steal, you know.
It's warm in the bay from the dome's waste heat energy too.
That's an-
You know what it is?
It's an autoreiv's core.
This one's a water-proof model,
and can be used as the Rabbit's transmission system.
"Rabbit"?
Right.
I'm not so spineless that I'd stick around here forever.
You seem to be thinking that I'm brash
because I'm blabbering so soon after we met.
I'm not-
You might have heard from Hoody,
but I'm known to be a weirdo.
But you know...
from my point of view,
the guys who are going on and on about being free
are the real weirdos.
Well,
I don't intend on living as a dome parasite forever.
Remember that.
Okay...
And you?
You've got your arms around your knees, moping and sulking.
Nothing.
Pino-chan's acting a lot more mature than you.
That might be right.
Well,
you'll get used to life here before long.
Take your time and figure out what you want to do...
Damn.
Run!
What's that?
A surveillance unit.
C'mon, hurry up!
Surveillance units?
Romdeau's unmanned scouting ships.
It takes the trouble of taking the
same route at the same time every day.
But as long as it doesn't find you, people won't look for you.
Well,
that's about how much we're worth to Romdeau.
Pino!
That idiot!
W-Wait!
Autoreivs are...
Pino, get down!
Hey,
I thought surveillance units don't shoot autoreivs.
I hope this doesn't turn into trouble.
This man...
He is Vincent Law.
What are your orders?
Why is he alive?
Will you report this to the Administrator?
No.
I'm sure he wouldn't be interested.
Instead, reinforce the patrol units.
They are already on standby.
Beautiful.
Request action from the relevant authorities.
However, the specimen's location has yet to be determined.
That's irrelevant.
Either way,
that man has the answers.
Right now...
I can tell.
That is unusual.
Your emotional words, that is.
I am surprised as well.
It is as though I myself have been infected by Cogito.
That is a joke I cannot laugh at.
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
Someone whispers:
"When something invisible becomes visible,
you can no longer stay yourself."
I still don't care-
meditation   summoning
if that is also who I am.